<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Getmoredonations Changelog RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Getmoredonations Changelog RSS Feed]]></description><link>https://getmoredonations.com</link><generator>RSS feed generator</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 08:06:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Multiple connections]]></title><link>https://getmoredonations.com/docs/changelog/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://getmoredonations.com</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;You can now create multiple integration connections to all of our integrated CRM services. This allow you to connect both your organization’s main instance and a sandbox instance to test and fine-tune your integrations. To add an additional integration to another instance of your CRM service, head to the Integrations section of your Dashboard settings and click “Add integration”. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stripe card renewal update]]></title><link>https://getmoredonations.com/docs/changelog/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://getmoredonations.com</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;In response to Stripe&amp;#39;s introduction of a 0.25 USD fee for automatic card update services, we&amp;#39;ve revised our payment method management. Automatic card updates will be utilized only for active recurring plans and not for one-time donations, thereby minimizing unnecessary fees while still ensuring seamless card updates for your recurring donors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Titles added for Germans]]></title><link>https://getmoredonations.com/docs/changelog/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://getmoredonations.com</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;German organizations can now opt to ask supporters for their title (Herr, Frau, Prof. or Dr.) To enable this option, to go the “Supporter” section of any campaign’s settings and enable the “Ask for title” checkbox. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CTA in list-type elements]]></title><link>https://getmoredonations.com/docs/changelog/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://getmoredonations.com</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;We’ve added the option for a “Donate” button to our Top Supporters, Top Locations, and Recent Donations Elements. With this addition, these three Elements will now also prompt action as well as showcasing other donors’ contributions. To enable this button, select the “Show donate button” checkbox in the Element settings. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Impact descriptions]]></title><link>https://getmoredonations.com/docs/changelog/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://getmoredonations.com</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;You can now boost generosity even further with impact descriptions, giving donors an idea of how exactly their donation might be used by your organization — “$50 feeds one family for a week”, for example. When added to a campaign, these impact descriptions will appear on both your Campaign Pages and in your Checkout modals next to each suggested amount. To start adding impact descriptions open the Settings tab in one of your campaigns and find the Suggested Amounts section. &lt;a href=&quot;/ba0803e0f24745a0bcc0585e6c55a367&quot;&gt;Learn more →&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Upsell in the DP ]]></title><link>https://getmoredonations.com/docs/changelog/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://getmoredonations.com</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Donors are now able to increase their recurring donation and/or start covering their donation transaction costs with the click of a single “Give more” button in the Donor Portal. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[VT redesign ]]></title><link>https://getmoredonations.com/docs/changelog/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://getmoredonations.com</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;We’ve redesigned our Virtual Terminal, making it even easier to use. The new full-page layout features a handy fixed summary of the donation on a side panel, meaning your Virtual Terminal operators can efficiently process donations while always having essential donation details like frequency, amount, and cost coverage immediately in sight. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Join existing P2Ps through elements]]></title><link>https://getmoredonations.com/docs/changelog/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://getmoredonations.com</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;You can now configure whether donors who interact with the P2P Link and P2P Button Elements can create a new fundraiser, join an existing one, or have both options. This allows you to run campaigns that have a set number of fundraisers for donors to select from, if desired. Access these options in the settings for your P2P Button and P2P Link Elements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[No auth to access tributes in DP]]></title><link>https://getmoredonations.com/docs/changelog/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://getmoredonations.com</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Donors who make tribute donations no longer require email authentication to enter the Donor Portal to add details of their dedication — they’ll be taken straight to the correct tribute editor through a unique URL. If you use a custom “Thank You” page, the new “donateId” parameter will allow you to set up the same process from that page. This change makes the tribute giving process easier and smoother for tribute donors, while also reducing the chances of unauthorized Donor Portal access. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thank you with PDF receipt ]]></title><link>https://getmoredonations.com/docs/changelog/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://getmoredonations.com</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Donor emails now include links to download receipts for increased convenience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>